Finding Aid for the Ephraim Sales Collection of Tapes and Transcripts of Interviews by Roy Newquist LSC.1494
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Moorehead, Agnes (Actress)., 98 (Box 7)
  - Agnes Moorehead, undated; yrlsc1494_007_098a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:59) (Box 7, Case 98)
  - Agnes Moorehead, undated; yrlsc1494_007_098b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:54) (Box 7, Case 98)
- Moorehead, Agnes (Actress)., 144 (Box 11)
  - Agnes Moorehead, Conversation between Roy Newquist and "Chuck", undated; yrlsc1494_011_144a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:29:00) (Box 11, Case 144)
    Content Note: First half of recording features interview with Agnes Moorhead; middle of recording features except from unknown script, or movie; last part of recording features personal conversation between Roy Newquist and "Chuck"
  - Agnes Moorehead, Conversation between Roy Newquist and "Chuck", undated; yrlsc1494_011_144b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:15:15) (Box 11, Case 144)
    Content Note: Side B is mostly silent except for the very begining and very end of the recording
- Morison, Brad ______. [Guthrie Theater]., 166 (Box 12)
  - Bradley Morison, Tyrone Guthrie, undated; yrlsc1494_012_166; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:59:38) (Box 12, Case 166)
- Morison, Brad. ______. [Guthrie Theater]., 173 (Box 12)
  - Bradley Morison, Tyrone Guthrie, Zoe Caldwell, undated; yrlsc1494_012_173a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:19:51); Condition Note: volume varies throughout recording (Box 12, Case 173)
  - Bradley Morison, Tyrone Guthrie, Zoe Caldwell, undated; yrlsc1494_012_173a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:46) (Box 12, Case 173)
- Morton, Fredric (Writer)., 186 (Box 13)
  - Fred Morton, 1965 June 4; yrlsc1494_013_186a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:28:12); Condition note: speed varies throughout recording (Box 13, Case 186)
  - Fred Morton, 1965 June 4; yrlsc1494_013_186b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:25:49); Condition note: speed varies throughout recording (Box 13, Case 186)
- Nathan, Robert (Writer). -- Transcript., 1965 February; (12pp.) (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Newman, Paul (Actor)., 83 (Box 6)
- Newman, Paul (Actor)., 111 (Box 8)
  - Paul Newman, George Peppard, undated; yrlsc1494_008_111a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:42); Condition Note: heavy buzz throughout recording (Box 8, Case 111)
  - Paul Newman, George Peppard, undated; yrlsc1494_008_111b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:55:47) (Box 8, Case 111)
- Newman, Paul (Actor) -- Transcript of Tape no.111., (33pp.) (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Newman, Paul (Actor)., 146 (Box 11)
- Newman, Paul (Actor) -- Transcript of Tape no.146., (25pp.) (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Newman, Phyllis (Actress)., 162 (Box 12)
  - Phyllis Newman, undated; yrlsc1494_012_162a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:41) (Box 12, Case 162)
  - Phyllis Newman, undated; yrlsc1494_012_162b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:16:51) (Box 12, Case 162)
- Newquist, Roy Notes to Himself, undated; yrlsc1494_013_190a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:41) (Box 13, Case 190)
  Content note: Roy Newquist discusses acting, actors, acting companies and theaters
- Nichols, Mike (Director)., 24 (Box 2)
- Nichols, Mike (Director)., 24 (Box 2)
- Nichols, Mike (Director)
- Nimoy, Leonard (Actor)., 134 (Box 10)
- O'Connor, Richard (Writer)., 102 (Box 8)
- O'Sullivan, Maureen (Actress)., 40 (Box 3)
- O'Toole, Peter (Actor)., 7 (Box 1)
  - Peter O'Toole, 1965 July 1; yrlsc1494_001_007a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:58:55) (Box 1, Case 7)
  - Peter O'Toole, 1965 July 1; yrlsc1494_001_007b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:06:35) (Box 1, Case 7)
- Oberon, Merle (Actress)., 143 (Box 11)
  - Merle Oberon, Richard Quine, undated; yrlsc1494_011_143a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:41:42) (Box 11, Case 143)
  - Merle Oberon, Richard Quine, undated; yrlsc1494_011_143b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:23:17) (Box 11, Case 143)
- Palance, Jack (Actor)., 35 (Box 3)
- Parson, Michael J. (Actor)., 31 (Box 3)
  - Denholm Elliott, Michael Parson, undated; yrlsc1494_003_031a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:41) (Box 3, Case 31)
  - Denholm Elliott, Michael Parson, undated; yrlsc1494_003_031b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:12:11) (Box 3, Case 31)
- Payne, Robert (Writer)., 155 (Box 11)
  - Robert Payne, 1964 April 1; yrlsc1494_011_155a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:07:58) (Box 11, Case 155)
    Content Note: Beginning of interview begins on Side B
  - Robert Payne, 1964 April 1; yrlsc1494_011_155a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:14:58) (Box 11, Case 155)
- Pearce, Alice (Actress)., 60 (Box 5)
  - Alice Pearce, undated; yrlsc1494_005_060a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:02:18) (Box 5, Case 60)
- Pearson, Hesketh (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 October; (7pp.) (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Peerce, Jan (Singer)., 52 (Box 4)
- Peerce, Jan (Singer)., 57 (Box 5)
  - Jan Peerce, undated; yrlsc1494_005_057; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:29:47) (Box 5, Case 57)
- Peerce, Jan (Singer)., 59 (Box 5)
  - Jan Peerce, undated; yrlsc1494_005_059a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:55) (Box 5, Case 59)
  - Jan Peerce, undated; yrlsc1494_005_059b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:45) (Box 5, Case 59)
- Peerce, Jan (Singer)., 72 (Box 6)
  - Unidentified authors, Paul Chevigny, Jan Peerce, undated; yrlsc1494_006_072a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:36:59) (Box 6, Case 72)
    Content Note: First half of recording features two separate interviews with unidentified authors regarding their books. Second half of recording features author, Paul Chevigny
  - Jan Peerce III, undated; yrlsc1494_006_072b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:36:44) (Box 6, Case 72)
- Peerce, Jan (Singer)., 87 (Box 7)
  - Two Unidentified Authors, Jan Peerce, undated; yrlsc1494_007_087a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:36:26) (Box 7, Case 87)
    Content Note: Side A features a discussion with a history author and a political science author
  - Two Unidentified Authors, Jan Peerce, undated; yrlsc1494_007_087b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:36:26) (Box 7, Case 87)
- Peerce, Jan (Singer)., 88 (Box 7)
  - Jan Peerce and Friends, Hortence Calisher, undated; yrlsc1494_007_088a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:36:20) (Box 7, Case 88)
  - Jan Peerce and Friends, Hortence Calisher, undated; yrlsc1494_007_088b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:36:05) (Box 7, Case 88)
- Peerce, Jan (Singer)., 110 (Box 8)
  - Jan Peerce, undated; yrlsc1494_008_110a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:39:48) (Box 8, Case 110)
  - Jan Peerce, undated; yrlsc1494_008_110b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:46:33) (Box 8, Case 110)
- Peerce, Jan (Singer)., 165 (Box 12)
  - Newquist's son, Jan Peerce, undated; yrlsc1494_012_165a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:05:03) (Box 12, Case 165)
    Content Note: first 11 minutes of the recording features Newquist's son playing with the tape machine
  - Newquist's son, Jan Peerce, undated; yrlsc1494_012_165b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:43:35) (Box 12, Case 165)
- Peerce, Jan (Singer)., 194 (Box 13)
  - Robert Kyle, Jan Peerce, undated; yrlsc1494_013_194a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:47) (Box 13, Case 194)
- Peppard, George (Actor)., 47 (Box 4)
  - George Peppard, Charlton Heston, undated; yrlsc1494_004_047a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:59); Condition Note: recording speeds up toward the end (Box 4, Case 47)
  - George Peppard, Charlton Heston, undated; yrlsc1494_004_047b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:00:00); Condition Note: heavy buzz throughout recording (Box 4, Case 47)
- Peppard, George (Actor)., 111 (Box 8)
- Perelman, S.J. (Writer)., 142 (Box 11)
  - S.J. Perelman, Bob Stein, undated; yrlsc1494_011_142a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:49) (Box 11, Case 142)
  - S.J. Perelman, Bob Stein, undated; yrlsc1494_011_142b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:26:54) (Box 11, Case 142)
    Content Note: Editor in chief of Redbook and McCall's Magazine
- Petrakis, Harry Mark (Writer) -- Transcript., (9pp.) (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Petrakis, Harry Mark, undated; yrlsc1494_001_003b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:27:29) (Box 1, Case 3)
  Content Note: features book review of The Odyssey of Kostas Volakis
- Preston, Robert (Actor)., 181 (Box 12)
  - Robert Preston, 1965; yrlsc1494_012_181b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:00:35) (Box 12, Case 181)
- Previn, Andre (Musician)., 33 (Box 3)
- Quine, Richard (Producer)., 66 (Box 5)
- Quine, Richard (Producer)., 143 (Box 11)
- Quinn, Anthony (Actor)., 30 (Box 3)
  - Anthony Quinn, Virna Lisi, undated; yrlsc1494_003_030a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:37:22) (Box 3, Case 30)
  - Anthony Quinn, Virna Lisi, undated; yrlsc1494_003_030b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:37:12) (Box 3, Case 30)
- Quinn, Anthony (Actor) -- Transcript of Tape no.30., (30pp.) (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Quinn, Anthony (Actor)., 58 (Box 5)
- Quinn, Anthony (Actor)., 107 (Box 8)
- Quinn, Yvonne (Writer)., 136 (Box 10)
- Ransahoff, Martin (Producer)., 33 (Box 3)
  - Martin Ransohoff, Andre Previn and Dory Langdon, undated; yrlsc1494_003_033a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:29:32) (Box 3, Case 33)
  - Martin Ransohoff, Andre Previn and Dory Langdon, undated; yrlsc1494_003_033b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:01:50) (Box 3, Case 33)
- Ransahoff, Martin (Producer) -- Transcript of Tape no.33., (1p.) (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Rathbone, Basil (Actor)., 17 (Box 2)
- Reed, Rex (Writer)., 75 (Box 6)
  - Evan Connell, Rex Reed, undated; yrlsc1494_006_075a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:43) (Box 6, Case 75)
  - Evan Connell, Rex Reed, undated; yrlsc1494_006_075b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:19:13) (Box 6, Case 75)
- Reed, Rex (Writer)., 139 (Box 10)
  - Rex Reed, undated; yrlsc1494_010_139a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:32); Condition Note: heavy background noise (Box 10, Case 139)
  - Rex Reed, undated; yrlsc1494_010_139b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:32); Condition Note: heavy background noise (Box 10, Case 139)
- Release forms (Box 14, Folder 1-5)
  - Forgeries. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Valid. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - No tapes. (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Renzi, Eva (Actress)., 103 (Box 8)
- Renzi, Eva (Actress) -- Transcript of Tape no.103., (10pp.) (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Renzi, Eva/Sharif, Omar, undated; yrlsc1494_008_104a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:49) (Box 8, Case 104)
- Rhodes, Evan (Writer)
  See: Miller, Merle
- Rice, Elmer (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 August; (12pp.) (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Richardson, Lee (Writer)., 161 (Box 11)
- Righteous Brothers (Musicians)., 39 (Box 3)
- Righteous Brothers (Musicians) -- Transcript of Tape no.39., (17pp.) (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Robertson, Cliff (Actor)., 84 (Box 7)
- Robertson, Cliff (Actor)., 130 (Box 10)
- Robertson, Cliff (Actor)., 193 (Box 13)
  - Cliff Robertson, Michael Caine, Robert Aldrich, undated; yrlsc1494_013_193a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:53) (Box 13, Case 193)
- Robertson, Cliff (Actor) -- Transcript of Tape no.193., (15pp.) (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Robertson, Cliff, undated; yrlsc1494_006_084a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:58) (Box 6, Case 84)
- Robertson, Cliff, undated; yrlsc1494_006_084b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:53) (Box 6, Case 84)
- Roddenberry, Gene (TV producer)., 134 (Box 10)
- Ross, Katharine (Actress)., 83 (Box 6)
- Ross, Katherine (Actress) -- Transcript., (4pp.) (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Ross, ______. ______ -- Transcript., (8pp.) (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Roth, Beulah (Writer)., 5 (Box 1)
  - Arthur H. Lewis, Beulah Roth, 1963 September 1; yrlsc1494_001_005; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:42:18) (Box 1, Case 5)
    Content Note: features review of Lewis' The Day They Shook the Plum Tree. Content Note: Second half of interview with Beaulah Roth
- Roth, Beulah (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.5., (4pp.) (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Rubenstein, Helena (Businesswoman) -- Transcript., (3pp.) (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Rudofsky, Boris (Opera critic)., 183 (Box 12)
- Russell, Rosalind (Actress)., 13 (Box 1)
  - Rosalind Russell, undated; yrlsc1494_001_013; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:04:07) (Box 1, Case 13)
- Russell, Rosalind (Actress)., 1965 March.; 116 (Box 9)
  - Rosalind Russell, undated; yrlsc1494_009_116; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:55:23) (Box 9, Case 116)
- Russell, Rosalind (Actress). -- Transcript of Tape no.116., 1965 March; (21pp.) (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Ryan, Cornelius (Writer)., 104 (Box 8)
  - Cornelius Ryan, undated; yrlsc1494_008_104b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:35:08); Condition note: speed increases toward end of Side A (Box 8, Case 104)
- Ryan, Cornelius (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.104., (3pp.) (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Ryan, Cornelius, undated; yrlsc1494_008_103b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:01:35); Condition note: speed is increased throughout recording (Box 8, Case 103)
- Ryan, Robert (Actor)., 114 (Box 9)
  - Robert Ryan, undated; yrlsc1494_009_114a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:54:04) (Box 9, Case 114)
  - Robert Ryan, undated; yrlsc1494_009_114b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:20:04) (Box 9, Case 114)
- Sanford, Isabel (Actress) -- Transcript., (5pp.) (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Schonberg, Harold (Music critic). -- Transcript., 1963 December; (22pp.) (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Schreider, Helen - Schreider, Frank (Writers). -- Transcript., 1963 September; (18pp.) (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Secret of Santa Vittoria. Notes for book about production -- Transcript., (6pp.) (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Segal, George (Actor)., 2 (Box 1)
- Segal, George (Actor)
- Selznick, Joyce (Motion picture executive)., 74 (Box 6)
- Selznick, Joyce (Motion picture executive)., 125 (Box 9)
  - Katharine Hepburn, Joyce Selznick, undated; yrlsc1494_009_125a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:02) (Box 9, Case 125)
  - Katharine Hepburn, Joyce Selznick, undated; yrlsc1494_009_125b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:57) (Box 9, Case 125)
- Selznick, Joyce (Motion picture executive) -- Transcript of Tape no.125., (25pp.) (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Selznick, Joyce (Motion picture executive)., 126 (Box 9)
  - Joyce Selznick, Warren Beatty, undated; yrlsc1494_009_126a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:41:21) (Box 9, Case 126)
  - Joyce Selznick, Warren Beatty, undated; yrlsc1494_009_126b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:58:43) (Box 9, Case 126)
- Several Anonymous Men, undated; yrlsc1494_013_194b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:15:27) (Box 13, Case 194)
- Shariff, Omar (Actor)., 49 (Box 4)
- Shariff, Omar (Actor)., 103 (Box 8)
  - Omar Sharif/Eva Renzi, undated; yrlsc1494_008_103a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:48) (Box 8, Case 103)
- Sharp, Margery (Writer)., 170 (Box 12)
  - Alan Sharp, undated; yrlsc1494_012_170; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:15:57) (Box 12, Case 170)
- Sharp, Margery (Writer)., 178 (Box 12)
  - John Crosby, Margery Sharp, yrlsc1494_012_178a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:57:42) (Box 12, Case 178)
  - Margery Sharp, 1963 November 1; yrlsc1494_012_178b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:03:57); Condition Note: recording is very muffled (Box 12, Case 178)
- Shaw, Irwin (Writer). -- Transcript., 1964 February; (15pp.) (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Shimkin, Leon (Publisher)., 65 (Box 5)
  - Leon Shimkin, undated; yrlsc1494_005_065a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:23) (Box 5, Case 65)
  - Leon Shimkin, undated; yrlsc1494_005_065b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:03) (Box 5, Case 65)
- Shimkin, Leon (Publisher) -- Transcript of Tape no.65., (62pp.) (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Shimkin, Leon (Publisher)., 95 (Box 7)
  - Leon Shimkin, undated; yrlsc1494_007_095a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:39:26) (Box 7, Case 95)
  - Leon Shimkin, undated; yrlsc1494_007_095b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:35:02) (Box 7, Case 95)
- Shimkin, Leon (Publisher) -- Transcript of Tape no.95., (44pp.) (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Sinatra, Frank (Actor) [friend talking about]., 146 (Box 11)
  - Friend of Frank Sinatra, Richard Schickel, Roy and "Chuck", Paul Newman, undated; yrlsc1494_011_146a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:34:43) (Box 11, Case 146)
    Content Note: features discussion regarding Frank Sinatra, Schickel's book, "The Disney Version", and a personal conversation between Roy and friend "Chuck"
  - Friend of Frank Sinatra, Richard Schickel, Roy and "Chuck", Paul Newman, undated; yrlsc1494_011_146b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:03:26) (Box 11, Case 146)
- Sinatra, Nancy (Actress)., 39 (Box 3)
  - Nancy Sinatra, The Righteous Brothers, undated; yrlsc1494_003_039a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:23) (Box 3, Case 39)
  - Nancy Sinatra, The Righteous Brothers, undated; yrlsc1494_003_039a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:08) (Box 3, Case 39)
- Sinatra, Nancy (Actress)., 77 (Box 6)
  - Susan St. James, Nancy Sinatra, undated; yrlsc1494_006_077a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:43) (Box 6, Case 77)
  - Susan St. James, Nancy Sinatra, undated; yrlsc1494_006_077b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:11) (Box 6, Case 77)
- Skinner, Cornelia Otis (Writer, actress)., 148 (Box 11)
  - Cornelia Otis Skinner, Unidentified Man, undated; yrlsc1494_011_148a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:30:26) (Box 11, Case 148)
    Content Note: end of recording features dictation by unidentified man
  - Cornelia Otis Skinner, Unidentified Man, undated; yrlsc1494_011_148b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:27:45) (Box 11, Case 148)
    Content Note: recording features dictation by unidentified man
- Smith, Gene (Writer)., 195 (Box 13)
  - Roy Newquist Notes to Himself, Gene Smith, undated; yrlsc1494_013_195a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:11:08) (Box 13, Case 195)
    Content Note: first half features notes to himself regarding Frank Sinatra
- Smith, H. Allen (Writer)., 19 (Box 2)
  - H. Allen Smith, undated; yrlsc1494_002_019a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:03:13) (Box 2, Case 19)
  - H. Allen Smith, 1965 January 1; yrlsc1494_002_019b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:31:57) (Box 2, Case 19)
- Snow, C.P. (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 October; (13pp.) (Folder 11, Box 18)
- Sommer, Elke (Actress)., 37 (Box 3)
  - Elke Sommer, undated; yrlsc1494_003_037a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:43:39) (Box 3, Case 37)
  - Elke Sommer, undated; yrlsc1494_003_037b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:19) (Box 3, Case 37)
- Spaak, Catherine (Actress)., 66 (Box 5)
- St. James, Susan (Actress) -- Transcript., (7pp.) (Box 18, Folder 2)
- St. James, Susan (Actress)., 77 (Box 6)
- St. James, Susan (Actress) -- Transcript of Tape no.77., (32pp.) (Box 18, Folder 1)
- St. John, Adela Rogers (Writer)., 184 (Box 12)
  - Adela Rogers St. John, undated; yrlsc1494_012_184a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:11:55); Condition note: speed varies throughout recording (Box 12, Case 184)
  - Adela Rogers St. John, undated; yrlsc1494_012_184b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:17:32); Condition note: speed varies throughout recording (Box 12, Case 184)
- St. John, Robert (Writer)., 25 (Box 2)
- St. John, Robert (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.25., (39pp.) (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Star Trek, undated; yrlsc1494_010_134a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:36:04) (Box 10, Case 134)
- Star Trek, undated; yrlsc1494_010_134b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:36:25) (Box 10, Case 134)
- Stearn, Jess (Writer). -- Transcript., 1964 January; (11pp.) (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Stein, Robert (Writer)., 67 (Box 5)
  - Counterpoint II: Bob Stein, Counterpoint II: Rona Jaffe, undated; yrlsc1494_005_067a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:34:16) (Box 5, Case 67)
  - Counterpoint II: Bob Stein, Counterpoint II: Rona Jaffe, undated; yrlsc1494_005_067b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:46) (Box 5, Case 67)
- Stein, Robert (Writer)., 142 (Box 11)
- Stevens, Stella (Actress) -- Transcript., (33pp.) (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Stewart, James (Actor)., 73 (Box 6)
  - James Stewart, undated; yrlsc1494_006_073a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:02) (Box 6, Case 73)
  - James Stewart, undated; yrlsc1494_006_073b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:50:02) (Box 6, Case 73)
- Stewart, Mary (Writer)., 1963 November.; 150 (Box 11)
  - Mary Stewart, 1963 November 1; yrlsc1494_011_150; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:44:36) (Box 11, Case 150)
- Stewart, Mary (Writer). -- Transcript of Tape no.150., 1963 November; (14pp.) (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Stone, Irving (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 August; (17pp.) (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Stroud, Don (Actor)., 32 (Box 3)
- Stroud, Don (Actor) -- Transcript., (19pp.) (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Susann, Jacqueline (Writer)., 36 (Box 3)
  - Jacqueline Susann, undated; yrlsc1494_003_036a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:36:56) (Box 3, Case 36)
    Content Note: Interview begins on Side B
  - Jacqueline Susann, undated; yrlsc1494_003_036b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:24) (Box 3, Case 36)
- Susann, Jacqueline (Writer)., 94 (Box 7)
- Swing, Raymond Gram (Radio commentator)., 179 (Box 12)
  - Raymond Gram Swing, 1964 February 1; yrlsc1494_012_179a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:22:07) (Box 12, Case 179)
  - Raymond Gram Swing, 1964 February 1; yrlsc1494_012_179b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:22:07) (Box 12, Case 179)
- Tandy, Jessica (Actress)., 161 (Box 11)
- Tandy, Jessica (Actress)., 167 (Box 12)
  - Jessica Tandy, Kristina Callahan, undated; yrlsc1494_012_167a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:23:57) (Box 12, Case 167)
  - Jessica Tandy, Kristina Callahan, undated; yrlsc1494_012_167b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:23:37) (Box 12, Case 167)
- Taylor, Elizabeth (Actress)., 2 (Box 1)
- Taylor, Elizabeth (Actress)., 154 (Box 11)
- Taylor, Elizabeth (Actress)
- Taylor, Robert Lewis (Writer). -- Transcript., 1964 March; (11pp.) (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Terkel, Studs (Writer)., 140 (Box 10)
  - Studs Terkel, undated; yrlsc1494_010_140; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:17) (Box 10, Case 140)
- Terkel, Studs (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.140., (24pp.) (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Tiffin, Pamela (Actress)., 34 (Box 3)